[ ♪ ♪ ♪ ]
[ ROARS ]
[ SCREAMS ]
[ CROWD SCREAMING ]
[ ♪ ♪ ♪ ]
ALICE : My name is Alice .
I worked for Umbrella Corporation in a secret laboratory
developing experimental viral weaponry .
There was an incident . A virus escaped .
Everybody died .
Trouble was
they didn 't stay dead .
This was the start of an apocalypse that would sweep the entire world .
The men responsible for this disaster took refuge underground
and continued to experiment with the deadly T-Virus .
They felt secure in their high-tech fortress .
But they were wrong .
[ ♪ ♪ ♪ ]
[ GUNSHOT ]
[ IN JAPANESE ] Biohazard terminated .
Central Shibuya .
Confirm ?
MAN [ IN JAPANESE OVER RADIO ] : I confirm .
Nice shooting .
And I lead three to one .
TOSHI : The night is young .
Plenty more fish in the ...
[ TOSHI SCREAMS ]
Toshi , are you okay ?
Toshi , where are you ?
[ SPEAKS IN JAPANESE ]
[ WHOOSH ]
[ SOLDIER YELLS ]
[ ♪ ♪ ♪ ]
[ MAN SPEAKING IN JAPANESE OVER PA ]
[ IN JAPANESE ] Sentry three respond .
We lost contact with another one .
OFFICER : Chairman Wesker . WESKER : Report .
Sir , a half-hour ago , we began to lose contact
with some of our perimeter sentries .
- How many have we lost ? - All of them .
And you waited 30 minutes to tell me ?
We thought it was a communications problem . I didn 't want to disturb you .
Give me the surface gate .
[ MAN SPEAKING IN JAPANESE OVER COMPUTER ]
- This is Chairman Wesker . MAN : Sir .
WESKER : Report your situation .
Everything is quiet here .
No sign of intruders ?
[ STATIC BUZZES ]
- Hotaka . OFFICER : We have movement .
Multiple targets .
WESKER : Surface gate , identify targets .
Repeat , identify targets .
[ IN ENGLISH ] Sir , Elevator 2 is moving .
I want security at that entrance .
[ ♪ ♪ ♪ ]
[ GRUNTING ]
[ GUNS COCK ]
[ ♪ ♪ ♪ ]
[ GUNSHOTS ]
Hey , boys .
Is that any way to treat a lady ?
[ ALARM WAILING ]
Tell security to flood the main entrance with nerve gas .
Sir , our men are still up there .
Any more questions ?
Intruders in Sectors 1 through 5 , 7 and 8 .
Reports of gunfire in Sectors 10 and 11 .
[ EXPLOSION ]
Stay at your stations .
All security protocols are now in full effect .
Lock down all elevators .
Seal all internal blast doors .
And I want damage reports .
[ ♪ ♪ ♪ ]
[ SOLDIER YELLS ]
[ SOLDIERS SHOUTING IN JAPANESE ]
[ ♪ ♪ ♪ ]
[ BEEPING ]
ALICE 1 : Come on , move .
ALICE 2 : Go , go . Everybody ... ALICE 3 : Get out .
COMPUTERISED VOICE : Turbulence . Turbulence . Turbulence .
Turbulence . Turbulence .
Turbulence . Turb - -
[ ♪ ♪ ♪ ]
Any last words ?
[ GASPS ]
How nice to finally meet the real you .
Hurts , doesn 't it ?
Well , that 's just the start of the bad news .
All those powers of yours :
Speed , strength , accelerated healing .
- Well , you can kiss all those goodbye . - What have you done ?
The serum I 've injected you with
is neutralising the T cells within your body .
Put simply
the Umbrella Corporation is taking back its property .
You just didn 't work out , so you 're being recalled .
[ ALICE GRUNTING ]
[ ♪ ♪ ♪ ]
I 'm what you used to be .
Only better .
Please wait .
Last words ?
Thank you .
For killing you ?
For making me human again .
[ ALARM WAILING ]
COMPUTERISED VOICE : Pull up . Terrain . Terrain .
Pull up . Terrain . Terrain .
[ COUGHING AND GRUNTING ]
MAN : This is Arcadia , broadcasting on the emergency frequency .
There is no infection .
We offer safety and security , food and shelter .
This is Arcadia , broadcasting on the emergency frequency .
There is no infection .
[ ♪ ♪ ♪ ]
ALICE : While I took revenge on Umbrella
the last handful of survivors took a chopper to safety .
They were headed for a town in Alaska called Arcadia .
We 'd received radio transmissions from there .
They offered food and shelter , safety and security .
A haven , free of infection .
[ ♪ ♪ ♪ ]
May 3rd , 1600 hours .
A hundred and seventy-seven days without signs of life .
I 'm at 58.37 degrees north
134.58 degrees west .
Closing in on the coordinates for Arcadia
but no signs of it on any map .
I hope Claire and the others made it .
[ ♪ ♪ ♪ ]
You 're not coming ?
Take care of the others .
Good luck , K-Mart .
Claire .
[ HELICOPTER WHIRRING ]
[ BEEPS ]
May 3rd .
1930 hours .
Arcadia .
No such place exists .
Just an empty field .
And a beach .
But we all heard the transmissions .
Someone must have sent them .
Someone must have brought all these people here .
But why ?
And where did they go ?
Day 177 . Signing off .
I don 't know if I can do this much longer .
What if I 'm the last one ?
What if there is no one else ?
No one to watch these tapes .
Is this my punishment
for letting all this happen ?
[ ♪ ♪ ♪ ]
Hey . Wait !
Wait , please ! Stop !
Hello .
Hello ?
Answer me .
[ CAWING ]
[ GRUNTING ]
ALICE : Hey , hey .
It 's okay .
Sorry about that .
But I had to get this thing off of you .
What is this ?
Who did this to you ?
Do you even know who I am ?
My name is Alice .
We met in the Nevada desert 18 months ago .
Any of this sound familiar ?
Mikey , Carlos , L.J. ?
K-Mart ?
You left in a helicopter
with a group of survivors headed for Alaska .
Arcadia , remember ?
ALICE [ ON RECORDING ] : Arcadia , remember ?
[ ♪ ♪ ♪ ]
ALICE : May 4th , 0800 hours .
Plotting a course for Prince Rupert in British Columbia .
I 'll pass Vancouver , drop down to Seattle .
After that , it 's San Francisco and the rest of the Western seaboard .
[ SIGHS ]
My passenger is still as talkative as ever .
Whatever that thing was , it was injecting her with some sort of drug .
Something that causes memory loss .
I just hope the effects aren 't permanent .
[ ♪ ♪ ♪ ]
CLAIRE : Your name
is Alice , right ?
ALICE : She speaks .
Look , I 'm sorry about back there .
I don 't know what happened .
I don 't remember anything .
I don 't even know my name .
It 's Claire .
Claire Redfield .
Claire ?
Sound familiar ?
Not really .
You 'll get used to it .
Perhaps you can cut me loose now .
We should get to know each other a little better first .
[ ♪ ♪ ♪ ]
City of Angels .
May 6th , 1800 hours , Los Angeles .
No signs of life .
Not even the undead .
Some must have burnt with the city .
But what about the rest ?
Oh , my God .
CLAIRE : What ?
Look over there .
Damn .
[ SIREN WAILING ]
BENNETT : It 's a plane .
It 's a plane !
I knew it . Ha-ha .
- I told you they would come . - Hey , we 're down here . Hello !
[ GROWLING AND SNARLING ]
No way we 're getting in there .
Where is he going ?
Why is he flying away ?
It 's not flying away .
- It 's circling . - Circling ?
Damn , he 's low .
Down !
What the hell is he doing ?
He 's gonna land .
He 's gonna land . Get the stuff out of the way .
- Land ? - Yeah .
Land .
That is one crazy son of a bitch .
[ ♪ ♪ ♪ ]
This may get a little rough .
Then cut me loose .
Thanks .
Just don 't do anything crazy , all right ?
Nothing as crazy as what you have in mind .
- Come on , Kim , move it . - I 'm trying .
Well , try !
All right , hold on .
Hurry , he 's coming .
Come on .
[ ENGINE SPUTTERING ]
Whoa !
[ GRUNTS ]
[ GROWLING ]
[ YELLS ]
[ GRUNTS ]
- Come on , pull it . Come on . - Come on , pull !
LUTHER : Good . Good .
Good work .
That 's it .
Good job .
[ ♪ ♪ ♪ ]
- Nice landing . - I think technically it 's called crashing .
Luther West .
Alice . That 's Claire .
Luther West . A pleasure to make your acquaintance .
- Hi , my name 's Crystal . BENNETT : No , no .
Enough with the introductions . So you 're here to help us , right ?
- Can you get us out ? - You from Arcadia ?
- What did you say ? - Are you from Arcadia ?
- What do you know about Arcadia ? KIM : They said they 'd help .
There are survivors . Civilisation and safety .
Infection free .
So they sent you , right ?
No .
But there are others out there like you ?
It 's just us .
There 's to be no rescue ?
I 'm sorry .
[ SCOFFS ]
- Sorry . - Look , don 't take it so bad .
They had their hopes up and ...
Thought you could take them to the promised land .
Angel Ortiz .
That was some fine flying .
Thanks .
[ ♪ ♪ ♪ ]
- What 's the prognosis ? - She 'll live .
Yeah .
You know , I have the strangest feeling
I know you .
[ CHUCKLES ]
Yeah , I get that a lot .
You 're a sports fan , huh ?
Do you like basketball ?
Not really .
No ? Oh .
Well , maybe just a fan
of fine timepieces .
[ GROWLING ]
Yeah .
- Luther here is our resident superstar . - Ah ...
So tell me about Arcadia .
What exactly do you know ?
Just from their transmissions .
We 've been receiving their broadcast all week .
Food and shelter , safety and security , no infection .
We thought they sent you .
We 've been launching flares for days to get their attention .
- Flares ? LUTHER : Yeah .
Who 's gonna see flares from Alaska ?
- Alaska ? - Alaska ?
Arcadia . I 've been there .
It 's in Alaska . It 's a town , or so we thought .
A town ?
I don 't think so .
Take a look .
At what ?
[ ♪ ♪ ♪ ]
ANGEL : You see ?
It 's not a town .
It 's a ship .
ANGEL : I recorded this from the shortwave .
MAN [ ON RECORDING ] : This is Arcadia , on the emergency frequency .
There is no infection .
We offer safety and security , food and shelter .
It 's the same message we heard .
They must have sailed down the coast , picking up survivors .
This is Arcadia , broadcasting on the emergency frequency .
[ STATIC BUZZES THEN HISSES ON RECORDING ]
What is that ?
I don 't know .
That was the last we heard from them .
Then it just stopped .
That was two days ago .
We 've been sending up flares on the hour .
So when you arrived , of course , we thought they sent you .
ALICE : Claire .
That ship over there .
That 's Arcadia .
I know .
- You remember ? - I remember the beach .
People were coming to help us .
What happened ? Why didn 't you go with the others ?
I don 't know .
I can 't remember .
ALICE [ ON RECORDING ] : We have to get to that ship .
We have to get to that ship .
[ FLARE HISSING ]
[ GROWLING AND GRUNTING ]
[ RUSTLING ]
[ THUDS ]
[ ♪ ♪ ♪ ]
Welcome to your new home , cell block B.
Crystal 's our cook .
The menu 's not extensive , but she is a master of what she does .
Sorry I didn 't bring better news .
Get used to disappointment , right ? That 's what my agent used to say .
Were you an actress ?
I came to Hollywood , ended up waiting tables .
Why are we waiting ? Excuse me . I 'm hungry . Thank you .
- Get out of here , man . BENNETT : Thank you .
I met plenty of creeps like him in my time .
What 's his story ?
Back in the world , he was some kind of big movie producer .
The boy 's got a stick up his ass .
Kim Yong used to intern for him . Still hasn 't figured the world has changed .
That plane , do you think it could still fly ?
It can fly , but it only seats two .
So take us to Arcadia one at a time .
Look , I think she was lucky to land here once .
Five or six times would be suicide .
Heh . No offence .
None taken .
There has to be another way out .
We have to get to that ship .
Well , there is the ...
[ LUTHER CLEARS THROAT ]
What ?
Nothing .
Look , it would be a waste of your time .
I have time to waste .
LUTHER : When the shit hit the fan , we took refuge in the prison .
It seemed like it had the biggest , strongest walls .
The best chance of keeping those things out .
By the time we got here , the guards and the inmates were already long gone .
I guess when people started eating one another
there wasn 't much point in keeping anybody locked up .
We thought the place was abandoned
until we made a discovery .
Wendell , time to take a break .
It 's about goddamn time . I hate being down here .
I 'm hearing movement in the walls .
So let 's check it out .
I 'll be back in a minute .
Come on .
[ ♪ ♪ ♪ ]
Name 's Chris .
You were the one flying that plane .
How do you know that ?
Wendell isn 't the only one that hears things .
I 'm glad you made it .
Maybe you can talk some sense into these people .
What do you mean ?
Isn 't it obvious ?
I 'm not a prisoner .
I shouldn 't be in here .
CHRIS : I was working with a military unit .
We were using this place as a staging post .
Things were already bad when the order came through to release all the inmates .
We needed as many people on the streets as possible
to fight those things .
And it was chaos .
We were pulling out and a gang of the prisoners jumped me .
I guess they thought I was a guard .
I woke up , my unit was gone .
I was in here .
Their idea of a joke .
You don 't believe me .
Do the others ?
You need to get me out of here .
- We 're all trapped here . - That 's true .
But I can help you .
LUTHER : Seen enough ?
ALICE : You find anything ? - No .
CHRIS : I know a way out of this place .
If you get me out of here , I 'll do the same for you .
You 're gonna need me !
Have you checked what he 's talking about ?
His way out ? Heh-heh .
He 's not telling us shit till we let him out .
And I 'm not letting him out .
The man is a killer .
- Really ? - I can see it in his eyes .
How can you be so sure ?
I know people .
- Interesting . - So tell me .
What do you see when you look into my eyes ?
LUTHER : Whoa .
Holy shit .
Girl 's gotta be prepared .
What would you possibly want with those ?
It 's a hobby .
A hobby ?
All right .
Well , I 'll see you in the morning .
[ ♪ ♪ ♪ ]
CLAIRE : No sign of anyone on deck .
Your friends are out there ?
I think so .
You don 't remember ?
It 's coming back .
Slowly .
Nothing that makes any sense .
[ SIGHS ]
[ TILES CLATTERING ]
[ SCRAPING IN DISTANCE ]
[ SCRATCHING ]
[ THUDS ]
[ ♪ ♪ ♪ ]
[ GROWLING ]
LUTHER : We still have running water .
ALICE : That 's very civilised .
We do our best .
It 's cold .
Our best only goes so far .
- These are for you . - Thank you .
I guess I should leave you to it .
I guess you should .
I 'll be right outside .
Thank you .
[ TILE CLATTERS ]
Luther ?
[ CLATTERING ]
- Take it easy , honey . - Move it .
Okay , I 'm just gonna be on my way now .
Okay , take it easy . Take it easy .
Get out of my sight .
[ ♪ ♪ ♪ ]
BENNETT : What is that smell ?
Must have burrowed up from the sewers .
LUTHER : Wendell said he heard things moving .
What ? So these things can just burst out anywhere ?
We gotta get out of this place .
Arcadia will send help .
No one 's coming to get us . Okay ? No one .
We have to help ourselves .
- This plane that you have . - Won 't hold everybody .
- Well , we can draw straws . ALICE : No .
We all get out of here and no one gets left behind .
Great .
How are we gonna do that ?
Walk out of here , just single file ?
BENNETT : Are you crazy ?
- They didn 't want him getting out . BENNETT : He 's dangerous .
Angel , what do you think ?
I think we don 't have much of a choice .
This is insane .
Crystal , Crystal , look at me . What do you think ?
- I mean , not even you 're that dumb . - I guess I am . I agree with Angel .
If this guy thinks he knows a way out , I wanna hear it .
All right .
BENNETT : Seriously ?
This is a mistake .
This is a big mistake . You better keep your eyes on him .
I was wondering how long it would take .
- Boo . - I ...
All right , let 's get the hell out of here .
Claire ?
What ?
Claire , it 's me .
It 's Chris .
I don 't know you .
CHRIS : Claire .
I 'm your brother , remember ?
What the hell 's happened to you ?
It 's okay . Let him go .
Look , she suffered some sort of memory loss .
If you really are her brother
it 'll come back .
All right , this is touching . Family reunion .
If we could just get a move on , please , before we 're all eaten the fuck alive .
[ ♪ ♪ ♪ ]
CHRIS : Behind those doors is a UPV , urban pacification vehicle .
The prison kept it in case of a serious riot .
Sixteen-wheeler , steel plate , water cannon . It seats 20 .
Ten tons of fun .
We roll on out in style , drive right over them .
The lock 's jammed . But we can cut through it .
When we hit the coast , we have to transfer to a boat .
- We 're gonna need more firepower . CHRIS : I got you covered .
When I was stationed here , we used the basement as an armoury .
It 's got every weapon you can dream of .
How do you know your unit didn 't take them with them ?
Because by the end
there were more guns than there were people to use them .
[ METAL CRASHES ]
You go get the guns . Luther .
Oh , my God .
What is this ?
They had pumps to keep the water out of the foundations .
When the electricity failed , some of the lower levels started filling up .
There 's another two floors down there .
And how far down is the armoury ?
All the way .
Luther , come on .
Get back . Get back .
Where do you think you 're going ?
I was a swim champ back in high school .
- Is that right ? - Here .
You 're gonna trust me with a gun ?
Yeah . Why not ?
Luther , just shoot that motherfucker .
What the fuck is that thing ?
[ ♪ ♪ ♪ ]
[ GASPING ]
[ COUGHING ]
All right . Let 's go .
[ CRYSTAL SCREAMS ]
[ ♪ ♪ ♪ ]
[ GROWLING ]
ALICE : Let 's go .
[ POUNDING ON DOOR ]
[ UNDEAD GROWLING ]
Nice .
[ ♪ ♪ ♪ ]
ANGEL : Damn .
[ UNDEAD POUNDING ON DOOR AND GROWLING ]
CHRIS : There must be hundreds of them out there .
We can 't go back that way .
- Oh , shit . - What do you mean , " oh , shit " ?
What ... ? What is this ?
What do you think it is ?
Don 't tell me that thing fits inside of there .
Can you put this back together ?
Maybe , but it could take a week .
What do we do now ?
I know .
Bennett
what have you done ?
[ GROWLING ]
Luther , we gotta get out of here . Come on .
[ GRUNTS ]
[ ENGINE STARTS ]
ALICE : Did you hear that ?
Come on , baby . Come on .
- What are we doing ? - Getting out .
- But the others . - Fuck the others .
Now , get on board .
LUTHER : Bennett , what are you doing ?
CLAIRE : Hey ! - Kim Yong ! Don 't do this .
Open this door .
Bennett , please .
LUTHER : Bennett !
Oh , shit !
That 's right , bitch . Fuck you .
Yes ! Yes !
Son of a bitch .
I 'm sorry . I 'm so sorry .
He 's headed for the Arcadia .
[ UNDEAD ROARING ]
Alice .
[ ♪ ♪ ♪ ]
Come on !
Head for the shower block .
- Move . - I 'll meet you there .
This thing has no power .
We won 't need power .
Oh , shit .
Hold on !
LUTHER : Hey , head to the shower block . Go .
[ ♪ ♪ ♪ ]
[ GRUNTS ]
Over here !
[ ♪ ♪ ♪ ]
- Are you all right ? - I 'm fine . Thanks .
This is some kind of joke , right ?
The tunnels lead to the sewers , the sewers lead to the storm drain .
This storm drain leads to the sea .
- It 's our only chance . - I 'll take point .
LUTHER : I got your back .
Ladies .
All right , you 're next .
- I can 't do it . - You can .
Let 's go !
[ ♪ ♪ ♪ ]
[ GRUNTS ]
[ YELLS ]
[ GUNSHOTS ]
[ GUN CLICKING ]
[ ♪ ♪ ♪ ]
[ GRUNTING ]
CLAIRE : Aah ! - Shh .
[ WHISPERING ] Those things are close .
We found a way out just down there . The tunnels drop into a storm drain .
Go . Be careful .
Where 's Kim Yong ?
Go . Go .
[ CLAIRE GRUNTING ]
I knew you 'd make it .
[ GROWLS ]
Luther !
LUTHER : Help !
[ ♪ ♪ ♪ ]
You can 't help him now .
We have to move on .
[ ♪ ♪ ♪ ]
No welcome party , huh ?
It looks like Bennett made it .
Let 's check inside .
- Did you find anyone ? - Nothing .
CHRIS : I checked the crew quarters . They 're all gone .
Looks like they left in a hurry .
MAN [ ON RECORDING ] : This is Arcadia
broadcasting on the emergency frequency .
There is no infection . We offer safety and security , food and shelter .
Fuel , power , everything 's running normally .
Look at this .
It 's the ship 's log .
The crew launched the lifeboats three days ago .
Exactly when the transmissions stopped .
CHRIS : But it says there are still 2000 survivors on board .
CLAIRE : We have to search every inch of this ship .
[ ♪ ♪ ♪ ]
Umbrella .
Of course .
I remember them coming for us .
[ K-MART SCREAMS ]
[ CLAIRE GRUNTS ]
This whole thing , Arcadia , was a lie .
No , it 's worse than that .
It 's a trap .
Where is everybody ?
I don 't understand .
I think I do .
They 're underneath our feet .
CLAIRE : They 're holding survivors to experiment on them .
Look .
It 's K-Mart . She 's here .
ALICE : Bring them up .
All of them .
[ ♪ ♪ ♪ ]
CLAIRE : Here she is .
K-Mart .
Get her out .
[ K-MART GASPS ]
K-Mart , it 's okay . It 's okay .
K-Mart , it 's all right .
I 'll get this off her . Let everyone out .
We 're your friends . Right now , we need your help .
Let me get this off you .
[ SCREAMING ]
[ ♪ ♪ ♪ ]
[ DOOR CLOSES ]
Why am I not surprised ?
You weren 't too hard to find .
Our satellite system is still operational .
And there aren 't too many people flying nowadays .
And besides , I always knew you 'd be drawn to your friends .
Loyalty , highly overrated .
[ SNARLING ]
Stop .
Down .
Wouldn 't want you harming my pets .
Drop your guns .
Thank you . Kick them to me .
Good .
You don 't look so good , Bennett .
Yeah , I 'm looking forward to playing with your pretty face .
What do you want from me ?
The T-Virus brought me back .
But it 's so strong .
It fights me for control .
I thought if I ingested fresh human DNA
I could redress the balance .
No wonder your crew abandoned ship .
WESKER : No matter .
Now I have a new subordinate .
And a new plan .
You were the only one who successfully bonded with the T-Virus .
Your DNA is stronger than the others .
I ingest you , I gain control .
[ ♪ ♪ ♪ ]
That 's pretty smart thinking .
There 's only one problem with that plan .
Stop right there .
And what is that ?
I 'm not on the menu .
[ ♪ ♪ ♪ ]
[ GROWLING ]
Well , isn 't this one big family reunion ?
Chris and Claire Redfield .
You 've really become quite an inconvenience for me .
I told you I 'd be bringing a few friends .
You should have brought more .
[ ♪ ♪ ♪ ]
[ GROWLING ]
[ GROANS ]
Aah !
[ WESKER GRUNTS ]
[ GROWLING ]
Claire . Claire !
Chris !
[ GASPS ]
[ ALICE GRUNTING ]
[ ♪ ♪ ♪ ]
Don 't even think about it .
Who the fuck are you ?
[ ♪ ♪ ♪ ]
[ GRUNTING ]
[ WHEEZING ]
I don 't think so .
[ ♪ ♪ ♪ ]
Don 't ... Don 't you shut them . I 'm a producer !
BENNETT [ OVER INTERCOM ] : Open those doors .
You are gonna deal with some serious consequences .
You motherfuckers .
Open the ...
You 're gonna live to regret this , all of you !
[ SLITHERING ]
Oh , God .
I just wanna go home .
[ BENNETT SCREAMS ]
Hey , it 's gonna be okay .
[ ENGINE WHIRRING ]
No .
Chris ! Alice !
[ ♪ ♪ ♪ ]
[ GUNFIRE ]
[ GUN CLICKING ]
[ BONES CRACKING ]
Come on !
[ DEVICE BEEPING ]
[ GASPS ]
- I didn 't want you to miss that . - Oh , heh , heh .
[ UNDEAD GROWLING ]
LUTHER : That 's right .
Star power , bitches .
[ ♪ ♪ ♪ ]
It 's a miracle .
I never dreamed there would be this many of us left alive .
So , what 's next ?
MAN [ ON RECORDING ] : This is Arcadia , broadcasting on the emergency freq - -
[ RECORDING CLICKS OFF ]
I say
we live up to the promise .
This is Arcadia , broadcasting on the emergency frequency .
Location 118.30 degrees west , 34.05 degrees north .
[ OVER SPEAKER ] There is no infection .
Repeat , there is no infection .
We offer safety and security , food and shelter .
If you are out there , we will help you .
There is hope .
[ ♪ ♪ ♪ ]
- What is that ? - Trouble .
[ A PERFECT CIRCLE 'S " THE OUTSIDER ( APOCALYPSE REMIX ) " PLAYS ]
♪ Disconnect and self destruct ♪
♪ One bullet at a time ♪
♪ What 's your rush now , Everyone will have his day to die ♪
♪ Lying to yourself again Suicidal imbecile ♪
♪ Think about it You 're pounding on a fault line ♪
♪ What 'll it take to get it through To you precious ♪
♪ Over this , why do you Wanna throw it away like this ♪
♪ Such a mess Why would I wanna watch you ♪
♪ Disconnect and self destruct One bullet at a time ♪
♪ What 's your rush now , Everyone will have his day to die ♪ ♪
JILL : Deployment in T-minus 57 seconds .
When you hit the deck , you watch your formation .
Take no prisoners and shoot to kill .
Total enemy numbers are unknown
but will include Umbrella fugitives and prime targets .
Claire Redfield , Chris Redfield and Project Alice .
So , people
whatever 's waiting for you out there , just know one thing :
You are gonna be in for the fight
of your lives .
[ ♪ ♪ ♪ ]
ALICE : Hey , boys .
Is that any way to treat a lady ?